BGM
Kaede, it's just so corps!
Yay!
Yes, I'm Kaede Sato, a corps member!
I'm Aruno Nakanishi, a 5th term student.
I'm Runa Hayashi, a 4th term student.
I'm Miyu Matsuo, a 4th term student.
I am Nao Tomisato, a 6th term student.
Yay!
It's our first time to get together.
Since we had our first meeting...
Today, Hayashi...
She's wearing red.
It's Kaede's idea.
I'm sorry. It's already white.
That's a very high percentage of white.
Didn't you think of wearing red?
It's an unspoken agreement.
I thought it was Norethode.
That's right.
The reason we're here today is...
We're here to get to know each other.
We're having a Mario party today.
Yay!
We're going to get people who've never played games or video games before.
So it's your first Mario party.
I'm glad we're having our first Mario Party together.
It's gonna be fun.
So today, we're going to have a Mario party.
I'd like to get to know you better.
And for those of you who play the mini-game and refer to it.
There's a reward of a sweet treat.
And while that person is eating their sweets.
The person who was absent will take his/her turn.
who was absent will take his/her turn.
There are five of us.
I don't know this person.
Who? Who?
I'll choose her.
I don't know her.
I don't know this girl.
Who's this girl?
He's cute!
Let's put her in the square.
He's so green and cute!
Well, let's make her face a square.
Most of the faces are...
Most of them.
We don't have any major characters.
Mobs like Ki no Pyo...
And there's a few who aren't in Mario...
Let's go to work once we get there.
They don't give us any hints at all.
Come on!
It's starting. Is everything okay?
I think I can practice once.
Who's the mole?
The mole. It's me.
Which one is me?
Meat.
I fell.
I fell?
Oh, my God, I'm scared.
I fell.
I see.
This hasn't started, has it?
It hasn't started.
But that's okay, right? It's good this morning.
You'll be following me all the way to the back.
You're counting on me.
I'm down.
That sounds fun. Do it.
Come on, Balin. Let's do it.
I'm so excited!
This is gonna be fun.
Movement features
Alba inclusive
I don't know which one is me.
I don't know why I chose it.
Don't go too far with this one.
You're all going too fast.
Why are you talking so much?
Final
Which one is it?
Movement
I don't know.
They're all so cute!
Matsuo, you're green, right?
That's right.
Which one is this red one?
That's me.
Wow, wow, wow.
Everyone's alive.
They're alive.
They're coming with me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm scared.
Nice fight.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I still do.
What?
Why? Why?
Why not?
Catherine.
What's going on?
I don't know. Everyone just disappeared.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I was playing it straight.
I need something.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you.
Let's go for your goal.
I'll give you a few seconds to eat a piece of fruit.
This is gonna be fun! Yoshi, you're on it!
We're on it! We're on it!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
This is fun!
Take it yourself.
Oh, my God.
You're so cute.
He's got a little techie in him.
I'll take that ring.
Aah!
That's scary.
Can't you just attack it or something?
I'm late.
Wait a minute.
How does it jump?
I can't attack it.
Oh, this one.
Cute guys.
Good tie, good tie.
Oh, my gosh! What's this cute cheese-looking thing!
So cute!
Oh! Who's that? Midori, you're fast!
Whoa! Aah!
Get away from me!
I can't go back for the apples.
I can't go back.
Matsuo and Nao?
Wait, wait, everyone's early.
Not so many apples.
I want apples.
I want apples, too.
I'm born.
Bounce on stone.
I'm bouncing off the stones
Bouncing off every stone.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's too much
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
Hey, hey, hey
There's something here!
Oh no, something's coming!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hey!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
Yes!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on, come on, come on.
I came in first, didn't I?
Oh, my God, stay with me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't climb! I can't climb!
I can't climb.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I can't climb!
Apples ate apples ate apples ate apples ate apples ate apples ate apples ate apples ate apples ate apples ate apples ate
Apples ate apples.
Hey.
Katherine.
Katherine, I'm just, uh...
I'm tired.
Katherine, hang in there.
Katherine, we're not done yet.
Arno's here, too.
It's okay. It's okay.
They'll get the message.
Hold on.
Arno, why aren't we moving?
How are we going to get there?
It's hard.
I still can't climb.
Go, go, go.
Arno's coming.
Hey, I still can't climb.
Come on, come on, come on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Help! Help!
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
Oh, oh, I'm sweating.
I'm sweating. Come on.
Yay! - Yay!
Force, force, force.
Oh, he's eating.
Who's that?
Oh, yeah, that's me.
Oh, that's funny.
No, it's not Asshaw. I'm not even on the good side.
Oh, yeah, I'm totally off the hook.
Why? What?
Original makeover.
I'll grab a rival with a crane.
Like Aku-Aku.
What?
Sounds fun.
But that one can still win.
The game just keeps getting better and better.
Hey.
Let's get started.
Scary, scary, scary, scary
I don't like it.
Oh, I'll get stuck
Oh, it's hard!
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
It's too fast!
Too fast!
Too fast.
It's a little...
This is gonna be hard.
Twenty-eight seconds to go.
Careful, careful, careful.
You're so cute.
It won't grow any longer.
It's cute over there.
Come on, Catherine.
Let's do it.
We'll do our best.
Watch out.
Catherine, we'll do our best.
Too dangerous.
Too hard.
Stop! Stop!
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
It's not dangerous.
This is too hard.
That's hard.
He's cute, he's happy.
What kind of counter will this be?
It goes 1 x 1 x 1.
You mean in total...?
Total counter.
What's this?
Overlapping shadows
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You two try to put this back together.
I see what you mean.
Go back to chat.
I'm that thing.
I see.
You're free to make your own decision.
Then, since the team went up, the Echigo-Tsumari Section has no choice but to hold up the decision.
That's why it's like a double.
That was quick!
This is it!
Oh, rar...
I'll upload higher
plus act 4
I'm lag
easier
Lag
ten Greet
sweets
So it's a reward?
Yes, that's right...
A reward already?
Here you go.
Here it is!
Strawberry tart.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
Please eat.
It looks like it's floating.
Bon appétit.
Okay, this pistachio-covered part.
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
It's good.
I've just been working on my head.
You're gonna need it.
It's good for the brain.
I'm glad you like it.
Have a good night and eat.
Good night, sir.
Good night.
Try to remember the progression of the fire by hip-dropping the fuse.
If we practice now.
The team that explodes loses.
And so on and so forth.
Practice, practice, practice.
I see.
We're gonna put out the fire.
Well, that was a bad idea. Super game.
All right, go, go, go, go, go!
I'm so excited.
It's two against two here.
Here we go.
Don't wait, don't wait, don't wait.
Oh, no!
Matsuo and Misato's team isn't doing well.
They're erasing at the same time.
That's good.
I'm going right.
Wait, wait!
Watch out!
This way, this way, this way.
Oh, shit!
Which way, which way?
We did it!
You won!
We won! We won! We won!
I just saw a tiny little thing...
It was going all the way to the back.
It noticed me, but I won.
I won!
We won!
Congratulations!
If you're in, I can't get in.
But it's so hard.
The height...
All right, I've got a good boy.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Katherine's good.
Katherine, she's stable.
Katherine's good. She's good.
Hey.
Oh, shit.
Oh, look out!
Hey, Mr. Matsuo.
No, no, no.
When I throw it, it's already in.
I'm just bouncing it.
That's good.
I'm Katherine.
Once it's in, it's in.
I don't know why they can't go up there.
How's it going up there?
Oh, my God!
That's great!
Nice voice, guys!
Nice Katherine!
That's really something, Catherine.
That's why you should have chosen Bowser!
Maybe it's important to choose the right character.
Hold it down?
Here?
Hold it down.
Are you holding it down one at a time?
Why don't you just hold it down?
I think it's okay to hold it down.
I can't do it at all.
Three.
Two.
One.
GO!
Definitely not Mr. Kayade, that's not the way to do it.
What's an emba?
Some of them you have to do twice to get into.
I think if you get the timing right, you can do it in one shot.
You can do it in one shot.
It's like chopped up.
Maybe I should just swing and gun it.
Catherine's.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Wheat or so it seems.
Oh, my God...
Come on!
Yay! - What?
What?
What's that?
Two again.
Yay!
What? That was fast.
That was fast.
That's amazing.
When did you do that?
I thought I was really good.
You're at the bottom of the list.
Of course.
I thought I was really good.
It doesn't matter if you're just barely there.
It's just a matter of finding an angle of view that's as close as you can get.
Where's the ice cream?
Ice cream?
Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Oh, there it is.
What? Why is it zoomed? Oh, I made a mistake.
I made a mistake. Why did you say zoom? He's crying.
What did you do with L and R?
It's a little out of square.
Oh, isn't that good?
Yes, it's good.
Is that Matsuo-san?
Hiraki jumped.
He went away.
Square's gone.
Why? Why? Why?
Matsuo, you're so good!
But, well, well, well...
What a ride!
He was on it so fast.
What a surprise!
Zoom in here.
Thank you.
To the right.
Where's the picnic?
I'm clear.
Where, where, where?
That's what you guys are doing.
Oh, no! I made a mistake.
Oh, well...
We're not giving up!
We're not giving up.
Let's go for it.
I don't need someone else.
Okay, okay.
Zoom in.
Get closer.
Closest.
But it's so messed up.
I should've gotten closer.
What? Oh, wait.
Oh, wait, I'm sorry.
But so close.
It's so close.
Oh, my God.
Where are you?
Eight.
I can find you as fast as anyone.
He's not here.
Worst, worst, worst.
I tried to zoom in and I pushed it.
All right, let's do it.
I don't see him.
I'm here. I'm here.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
It's so heavy.
Oh, no, that's not it. I'm sorry.
It's that one.
That's too bad.
That one's really heavy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, me?
You're all so good.
Smile.
Who's that?
Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God.
I want to do it again.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
They're so close.
Everybody's close.
Maybe I didn't need the one on the right.
Yay!
Is it low?
Is it too low?
But we won!
How did we win?
Oh, my gosh!
He's moving so fast!
What is this? What's the difference?
I see.
Tricycles are hard.
The side is up.
I have trouble with feet
easy, easy, easy
Tricycle is difficult
I have trouble with legs
Tricycle difficult
3 3 pretty chain is this
artists ah yarn
tig but so gives
Good, good, good!
Echo, are your legs a little longer than everyone else's?
You're short, obviously.
What are you doing?
Come on. Come on.
I'm in.
I lost!
We did it!
Did you see the echo?
But it's been stuck there the whole time.
Well, what do you think?
I knew it.
It was off the screen.
It's hot.
That's good.
Yay!
Cannulé.
What a stylish canele!
Bon appétit!
What do you think?
It's a delicious type of canele!
Delicious!
That's good.
You're a smart guy.
Hey.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
Digging a tunnel.
ZL here.
This is fun!
This is so much fun!
Here, here, here.
Is this it?
It's so beautiful.
All right.
Oh, my God.
You can't see it.
I'm trying.
There you go.
That was fast.
Here it comes.
First one.
I did it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What does that mean?
It's a chicken race.
I don't know.
I'm being forced to follow your example.
A, right?
Right there.
Oh.
He's going to fall off, isn't he?
I see.
He looks cold.
All right.
That's a long time.
I don't know. I don't know.
Where's the wall?
I'm still assuming.
Wait, maybe I'm early.
I'm pretty sure I can do this.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nine ways, right?
ni
So cute!
It's so cute!
Oh, it's gonna get erased.
I'm gonna get erased.
I can't do it anymore.
Hey, why are you flying?
I'm losing, I'm losing, I'm losing, I'm losing, I'm losing, I'm losing
Oh no, oh no, oh no, we're losing, we're losing, we're losing, we're losing, we're losing
Losing, losing, losing, losing, losing, losing, losing, losing, losing, losing, losing, losing!
I'm a believer
It's so pink!
Acid S
No?
Too much pink
I don't like it.
Look like.
What?
Look like...
We beat Isasir!
You guys are so strong!
Planning...
Zaruma defeat
Am I catch wrong!
Bakodeshi
sowie
It's not so bad, but it's hard!
Looks hard!
You guys are awesome!
Don't drop me!
Get out of the way, you son of a bitch!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You gotta be kidding me.
Oh, my God, he's dead.
Get the fuck out of the way.
Well, look at that.
Oh, my God.
I wasn't paying attention.
That's the first time I've ever won.
I didn't know your name was Gabon.
I've never heard of it.
I've never heard that name before.
I've never heard of that name.
I beat him because he made me feel threatened.
Here you go.
Lia.
Ice.
Oh, my God! I fell.
When I jump on my son, he falls off.
Okay, okay.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, he's dead.
Oh, no, don't move.
Here we go.
Oh, where did that come from?
Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bye-bye!
If I don't do that, I'm really gonna fall.
Catherine, go.
It's hard.
Midori is holding on for dear life!
Gabon!
Gabon, you're so cute!
I know you'll do your best
Gabon is so tiny!
He's just trying to get on his feet.
hahahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
はぁはぁはぁはぁ 惜しいとこでうちちゃんだから面白い
Oh, just hit the switch
It's so simple!
This is so much fun!
That's great!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Stop it!
Don't disrupt everyone's rhythm!
It wasn't me.
Who?
Me?
It's you, Kaede.
I'm sorry.
If it's Kaede, I'm sorry.
Deliberation, deliberation...
Mizuki songs
Suddenly the night candidates to the children's game
Coronavirus is moving 신기기
Then I want to bring sweets
This is a sweet potato
I've never seen it before
JoJo John
Looks delicious.
Well, I'm done, finally.
Here's your sweet potato.
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
All my hard work was worth it.
He looked at me and said.
I'm doing my best, and sometimes...
I'm doing my best.
I'm glad.
What kind of thing?
Wait, I've seen this before... in a video.
I can never do that!
I have to ride the sound.
He can't ride the sound.
I'm already on it.
Pointe.
Hoi! Hoi! Hoi!
Maintenance
You're not getting any help.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
How's it going?
I think I'm...
I'm...
Oh, no! Oh, no!
You're kidding, right? No way!
It's full of fairy tales!
Yeah, yeah!
We've got to do it!
What was that?
We made it, didn't we?
Nice try!
Strong!
Yes! Why?
Yes! - Yes!
OK, OK, OK, OK, Wheaker.
Start it up!
What? Did you see it move?
I'm moving with you.
That was really good.
I don't know. It never seems to be just right.
Me neither.
I can't get the right ingredients.
Just right!
That was fast!
Then it's good!
It's early!
Just right!
That was good.
I'm quick!
His!
Something too rich.
Not so good.
Not this time.
I think I can make it quick.
Oh, my God!
I'm so scared!
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
That's good!
Good job!
Oh!
We're the same!
I'm...
What's that?
Huh? Panchost?
Actually...
But I already ate this.
I don't want it.
I'll take it.
Maybe Matsuo will take a break.
Take a break?
Too much?
A little more.
I'll take your word for it.
Yes, for Matsuo-san.
What? What's this?
Packaged cake.
Isn't it too cute?
It's so cute.
Bon appétit. What flavor is that?
I can't get it off.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It's good.
It's good. I haven't eaten.
How is it? Is it really good?
It's good.
Tastes like boo-boo.
Boo Boo stings. I'm glad I tried.
Hey, the party's over.
I hope you deepened your silence.
There was a lot of effort put into it.
I don't care if you're a senior or a junior...
We said and did a lot of things.
It was fun.
Hey...
Well then, Kaede, let's continue to get along well with each other.
Let's continue to get along well with each other.
Yes, ma'am.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
There's something in here.
Raisins?
It's in the dough.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
It stinks.
It's very tasty.
Then eat a lot.
Thank you very much.